T. James Crawford papers, 1940-1987 C468
Indiana University Archives
- Professional activities, 1948-1986; Undated (Box 4)
  - Professional organizations and conferences, 1948-1985; Undated (Box 4)
    - Indianapolis Business Education Council, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
    - National Association for Business Teacher Education (Box 4)
      - General (Box 4)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 4)
        - 1969-1970 (Box 4)
      - Agenda -, May 4-5, 1969 (Box 4)
      - Board Agenda -, May 8-9, 1970 (Box 4)
      - Board Meeting, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
      - Constitution, Nominations, etc., 1976-1977 (Box 4)
      - February Meeting, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
      - Guidelines, 1979 (Box 4)
      - Letters - Advertising in February, 1968 (Box 4)
      - Nomination, 1977 (Box 4)
      - Review, Undated (Box 4)
    - National Business Education Association, Articles, 1964 (Box 4)
    - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education - Eastern Illinois University, Report, 1971; (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - North Carolina Agricultural and Technical State University, October 3-4, 1969 (Box 4)
    - North Carolina Business Education Association, Fall Conference, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Speaking Engagements, 1957-1958 (Box 4)
    - Summer Conference, 1987 (Box 4)
  - General, 1948-1985; Undated (Box 4)
    - Advisory Committee on Teacher Education, 1961-1963 (Box 4)
    - Airborne Television, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Annual Salary Review, Spring, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Appendix to the General Report - Report of the School of Education, Indiana University to the National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1963; (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - Articles Critical of Business Education, Undated (Box 5)
    - Awards and Certificates, 1982-1985 (Box 5)
    - Business Education Accomplishments, Undated (Box 5)
    - Business Education - Facts, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Business Education - Indiana, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Business Education - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 5)
    - Business Education - State of Indiana Enrollment Statistics, 1977 (Box 5)
    - CPS (Certified Professional Secretary) Course of Study Proposal, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Changes in Departmental Title and Course Offerings, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
    - Class Reunion - Class of 34, Pittsburgh, PA, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Commission of International Education, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Committee Appointments, 1970-1978 (Box 5)
    - Committee on Relations with Ivy Tech, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Communications from President's Office, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Curriculum, 1967-1978 (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Changes (Box 5)
      - General, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Approved by School of Business Faculty 4-23, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Dean's Annual Report of the School, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
    - Departmental Administration, 1962-1979 (Box 5)
      - General (Box 5)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 5)
        - Fall, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
        - Spring, 1979 (Box 5)
      - Procedures Study Reports, 1962-1963; (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Doctoral Committees, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Dr. Crawford, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Dr. Earl Dvorak, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Esther D. Bray Testimonial Dinner, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Elvin & Artista Eyster, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Elvin S Eyster Biographical Material, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Eyster Memorial Resolution (copies), 1978 (Box 5)
    - Eyster Testimonial, April 23, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Annual Summary Report (Box 5)
      - 1948-1958 (Box 5)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 5)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 5)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 5)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 5)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 5)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 5)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 5)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 5)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 5)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 5)
      - 1977 (Box 5)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5)
      - 1979 (Box 5)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
    - Fifth-Year Core Requirements, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Ford Foundation Report, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Fort Wayne Proposals, 1973-1976 (Box 5)
    - The Gregg Award, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Gregg Award Letters, 1980-1982 (Box 5)
    - Guidelines for Vocational Business and Office Education in Indiana, Undated (Box 5)
    - Halterman (News Release on Death), Undated (Box 5)
    - Indiana University Secretarial Assistantship Program, 1965-1967 (Box 5)
    - Indiana University Training and Development Programs, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Indiana State Plan for Vocational Business and Office Education, 1965 (Box 5)
    - IU Vocational Education Program, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Indianapolis Business Education Department, 1978 (Box 5)
    - International Business Education, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Indianapolis Campus Equipment Repair, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Information for Dean's Annual Report - T. James Crawford, 1979-1980 (Box 5)
    - Interim Report, 1962 (Box 5)
    - International Research, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
    - Ivy Tech (Box 5)
      - General, Undated (Box 5)
      - Proposal, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Jamaicans Visit to Indiana University, April 16-18, 1975 (Box 6)
    - MBA Track in Business Education, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Materials Submitted for Annual Report, June 2, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Materials for Dr. Crawford's Nomination for Teaching Award, 1982 (Box 6)
    - McCain, Judy - Proposal, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Patricia Medrano - Visiting Lecturer, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
    - Memo on Tenure and Dossier Preparation, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Minutes - Administration Communications Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous Materials, 1968-1978; (3 folders) (Box 6)
    - Monroe County Community School Corporation Clerical-Secretarial Study, 1975 (Box 6)
    - New Course Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1976 (Box 6)
    - Newspaper Releases, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
    - Open House (Box 6)
      - Christmas, 1974 (Box 6)
      - Christmas Party, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Plaque Signatures, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Proposal for Course Changes, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Proposal for Two-Year Administrative Assistant Program, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Proposed Changes in Department Curriculum, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Proposed Curriculum Changes, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
    - Publicity Releases, 1965-1978 (Box 6)
    - A Report on an Evaluation of Programs in Business Education at North Carolina Agriculture and Technical State University, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Report on Business Education for NCATE Evaluation, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Salary Review Meeting - 1/28/82, 1982 (Box 6)
    - School of Business (Box 6)
      - Department Prospectus, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
      - Tenure, 1971-1974 (Box 6)
    - School of Education (Box 6)
      - Announcements, 1957-1958 (Box 6)
      - Instruction and Curriculum, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Significant Challenges to Education and Business, Undated (Box 6)
    - Skill Survey (Peggy Saylors), 1973 (Box 6)
    - Slaughter Luncheon, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - State Administration Study, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Suggestions for Research, 1959 (Box 6)
    - A Supplement to the General Report - Report of the School of Education, Indiana University to National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Television Typewriting, 1957 (Box 6)
    - Term Report, Undated (Box 6)
    - Travel Information - Caribbean Area, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Travel Request and Vouchers, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Visiting Scholars Program - Piedmont University, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
    - Vocational Education Act of 1963 (Box 6)
- Publishing, 1940-1986; Undated (Box 6)
  - 20th Century Typewriting (Box 6)
    - General, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Laboratory Materials (Box 6)
      - Part 1 and 2, 1962 (Box 6)
      - Part 3 and 4, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Teacher's Manual, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Abstract, 'The Effects of Emphasizing Production Typewriting Contrasted with Speed Writing', 1956 (Box 6)
  - Articles Written, 1976 (Box 6)
  - At the Start of a New Decade--TJC--Balance Sheet, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Frequency of Use of Gregg Shorthand Prefixes and Suffixes - Crawford, 1940 (Box 6)
  - Gregg Publishing Company - Tony Weber, 1979 (Box 6)
  - South-Western Publishing Company, 1965-1986; (5 folders) (Box 7)
  - Dr. H. D. David, 1970-1986 (Box 8)
    Scope and Contents
    (office files)
    Restricted
  - Personal Correspondence, 1958-1963 (Box 8)
    (Series: Teaching, Subseries: General)